{
    "subject": "resource/Church_of_St._George_(Cairo)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Old_Cairo",
    "human_readable": "The Church of St. George (Cairo) is about Old Cairo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9077358245849609,
            "question": "Are there other religious structures in Old Cairo besides the Church of St. George?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8858016729354858,
            "question": "What can you tell about Cairo's history based on the presence of the Church of St. George?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6077972650527954,
            "question": "What historical area is the Church of St. George associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5782886147499084,
            "question": "Where is the Church of St. George located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46551239490509033,
            "question": "Is the Church of St. George a modern structure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3657587170600891,
            "question": "Does the Church of St. George hold any special religious significance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3612697124481201,
            "question": "What architectural style is typical of the Church of St. George?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3598874509334564,
            "question": "Why might the Church of St. George be considered an important landmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3263891935348511,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist activities near the Church of St. George?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2846963405609131,
            "question": "Has the Church of St. George undergone any renovations or restorations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Church of St. George (Cairo) is about Old Cairo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4030_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist activities near the Church of St. George?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4030_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might the Church of St. George be considered an important landmark?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4030_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What architectural style is typical of the Church of St. George?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4030_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4030_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention the Church of St. George in Old Cairo, and describe it as being located in the heart of Old Cairo, with nearby historical sites and a monastery also mentioned."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the Church of Saint George is located in Old Cairo, supporting the statement that the church is about Old Cairo."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}